A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.14-SG 1.15 (A88-A89) FA478
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 89), 1973-2005; 1982-1988; 1.15; 42.49 Cubic Feet
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - Children's Books Feasibility Study (AH 8539), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 155-159)
      Folder 159 - Supplementary Material
    - Five Colleges, Inc. - Humanities Network (AH 8540), 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 160)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Visiting Scholar Data Base (AH 8549), 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 161)
    - Repertory Dance Theatre (of Utah) - 20th Anniversary Performances (AH 8602), 1985-1988 (Box 30, Folder 162)
    - Group I Acting Company, Inc. - "ORCHARDS: Seven American Playwrights Present Stories by Chekhov" (AH 8603), 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 163-164)
    - New York City Opera - Fire Emergency Fund for Sets and Costumes (AH 8605), 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 165-166)
    - Readers International - Contemporary Non-Western Literature (AH 8611), 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 167-168)
      Folder 168 - Supplementary Material
    - Downtown Community Television Center, Inc. - Building (AH 8617), 1986-1990 (Box 31, Folder 169-170)
    - Center for Understanding Media, Inc. - Picture Opera (AH 8618), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 171-172)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers-Civic Responsibility Conference (AH 8631), 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 173-174)
    - Minnesota Composers Forum - American Music (AH 8637), 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 175)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - University of Georgia - Wildlife Management in Suriname (AS 8506), 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 176)
    - International Society for Plant Molecular Biology - International Congress (AS 8508), 1983-1986 (Box 33, Folder 177)
    - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases - Hans Jahnke (AS 8509), 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 178)
    - International Fertilizer Development Center - Denitrification Losses (AH 8512), 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 179)
    - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center - Wide Cross Program on Wheat (AS 8514), 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 180)
    - International Trypanotolerance Centre - Consultant (AS 8518), 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 181)
    - International Service for National Agricultural Research - Consultants (AS 8519), 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 182)
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Achola Okeyo (AS 8520), 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 183)
    - Philadelphia Society for Promoting Agriculture (AS 8525), 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 184-185)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Tissue Culture Laboratory Equipment (AS 8526), 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 186)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management - Fund Raising Program (AS 8529), 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 187-188)
    - Fudan University - Institute of Genetics (AS 8531), 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 189)
    - Max-Planck-Institute for Plant Breeding - Electrotransformation (AS 8533), 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 190)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - W. Thomas Conelly (AS 8534), 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 191)
    - University of Florida - Gender Issues in Farming Systems (AS 8540), 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 192)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Publication, Rice Genetics (AS 8541), 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 193)
    - Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization - Tissue Culture (AS 8542), 1983-1987 (Box 35, Folder 194, Box 36, Folder 195)
    - University of California (Davis) - Salt Tolerance in Cereals (AS 8601), 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 196)
    - Biotechnology of Cereal Crops - Workshop (AS 8602), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 197)
    - World Resources Institute - World Bank and International Agricultural Development (AS 8605), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 198)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Symposium on Chromosome Engineering in Plants (AS 8613), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 199)
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Review (AS 8617), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 200)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Workshop on Biotechnology for Crop Improvement (AS 8623), 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 201)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management - Tilapia Breeding (AS 8631), 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 202-203)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - Baylor College of Medicine - Conference on High School Math and Science Improvement Programs (EO 8502), 1984-1986 (Box 37, Folder 204)
    - City College of New York - Bridge to Graduate Study in Science Program (EO 8504), 1982-1987 (Box 37, Folder 205-207)
    - Exploratorium - Explainer Program (EO 8509), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 208)
    - Tulane University - Conference on Voting Rights and the Democratic Process (EO 8510), 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 209-210)
      Folder 210 - Supplementary Material
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #1B, 2017:FA478:003 (Box 38, Folder 210)
        Video cassette tape
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #2B, 2017:FA478:004 (Box 38, Folder 210)
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #3B, 2017:FA478:005 (Box 38, Folder 210)
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #4B, 2017:FA478:006 (Box 38, Folder 210)
    - Inuit Circumpolar Conference - Alaska Native Review Commission, Study of Alaska Native Claims Settlement Act (EO 8512), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 211-214)
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education, Inc. - Citizen Empowerment Project (EO 8514)), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 215)
    - University of Michigan - National Black Election Study (EO 8515), 1983-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 216-221, Box 40, Folder 222-224)
    - Ellen Lewin - Gender Role Grant (EO 8518), 1985-1987, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 225-226)
    - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Women and Pensions (EO 8519), 1985-1986, 1988, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 227)
    - University of Michigan - Dual-Family Child Support (EO 8522), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 228)
    - Southern Education Foundation - Continuing Conference in Public Policy and Education (EO 8524), 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 229-233)
      Folder 233 - Supplementary Material
    - New York Urban League - Membership Campaign (EO 8525), 1985-1988 (Box 42, Folder 234)
    - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation, Inc. - Conference on the Economic Status of Black Women (EO 8529), 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 235)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies, Inc. - Conference of Black Scholars (EO 8530), 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 236)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc. - Special Committee of the Board (EO 8531), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 237-238)
    - University of Illinois - Sex Composition of Occupations, 1970-1980 (EO 8533), 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 239, Box 43, Folder 240)
    - Urban Institute - Child Care and Self-Sufficiency for Welfare Mothers Project (EO 8537), 1981-1991 (Box 43, Folder 241-245)
    - Institute for Puerto Rican Policy, Inc. - Hispanic Voter Registration Trends in New York City (EO 8538), 1985-1989 (Box 44, Folder 246-247)
    - Cornell University - National Conference on Economic Dislocation and Job Loss (EO 8541), 1983-1986 (Box 44, Folder 248)
    - Carol B. Stack - Culture of Gender Among Women and Men of Color (EO 8542), 1985-1989 (Box 44, Folder 249)
    - National Opinion Research Center - Youth and Labor Market (EO 8607), 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 250, Box 45, Folder 251)
    - Piton Foundation - Concept Paper, Denver Underclass (EO 8627), 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 252)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - Queensland Institute of Medical Research - Diagnosis and Prevention of Flavivirus Infections (HS 8503), 1984-1986 (Box 45, Folder 253)
    - Ferrucio Santoro - Study to Develop Vaccine Against Leishmaniasis (HS 8506), 1982-1987, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 254)
    - University of Victoria - Molecular Studies on African Trypanosomes (HS 8513), 1984-1986 (Box 45, Folder 255-256)
    - Mahidol University - Studies of Infection and Morbidity of Helminth Parasites (HS 8516), 1982-1986, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 257-258)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Conference on Medical Education and the Humanities (HS 8523), 1985-1987 (Box 46, Folder 259)
    - University of Oxford - Study of Thalassemia in Pacific Islanders (HS 8527), 1985-1987 (Box 46, Folder 260)
    - Harvard University - Cross-Cultural and Geographic Psychiatry (HS 8528), 1982-1986 (Box 46, Folder 261-262, Box 47, Folder 263-264)
    - Pei-yuan Chen (HS 8532), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 47, Box 265)
    - Princeton University - Dynamics of Infection and the Evaluation of Vaccination and Other Control Programs (HS 8533), 1982-1986 (Box 47, Folder 266)
    - International Epidemiological Association, Inc. - Costs of Regional Meeting and Distribution of "A Dictionary of Epidemiology" (HS 8535), 1984-1987 (Box 47, Folder 267)
    - International Federation of Scientific Editors' Associations - International Symposium on Scholarly Publishing and Development, Nairobi (HS 8536), 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 268)
    - Ministry of Health, Zimbabwe - Blair Research Laboratory - Research on Praziquantel (HS 8541), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 269)
    - New York University - Malaria Studies In Africa (HS 8543), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 270)
    - Leonardo Mata - Analysis of Puriscal (Costa Rica) Study (HS 8548), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 271)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Stipend and Health Insurance (HS 8549), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 272)
    - London School Of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Leishmania Meeting (HS 8552), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 273)
    - United Nations World Health Organization - Regional Office for Africa (HS 8554), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 274)
    - University of California (Los Angeles) - Symposium on Molecular Strategies of Parasitic Invasion (HS 8555), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 275)
    - Rollin B. Johnson - Nutrition and Parasitic Disease in Wild Baboons in Tanzania (HS 8556), 1983-1986, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 276)
    - University Hospitals (Cleveland) - Differences in Onchocera [sic] volvulus (HS 8601), 1984-1988 (Box 48, Folder 277)
    - Thomas G. Egwang - Research Project on the Development of Drugs for Filariasis (HS 8602), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 278-278A)
      Folder 278A - Closed material (Medical information)
    - Phyllis K. Freeman - Research Project on the Development and Distribution of New Vaccines (HS 8603), 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 279-280)
    - University of Connecticut - Research Project on Schistosomiasis (HS 8605), 1984-1989 (Box 49, Folder 281)
    - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Research on Leprosy (HS 8606), 1984-1989 (Box 49, Folder 282)
    - World Federation for Medical Education - Conferences (HS 8609), 1985-1988 (Box 49, Folder 283)
    - United Nations World Health Organization - World Health Assembly (HS 8620), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 284)
    - James M. Ntambi (HS 8630), 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 285)
    - U.S. and Thai Health Officials - Consultative Meetings (HS 8632), 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 286)
    - Emory University, Carter Center - Global Health Consultation (HS 8644), 1986, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 287)
    - Luis Rosero-Bixby - Effect of Fertility Decline on Infant Mortality in Costa Rica (HS 8851), 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 288)
  - International Relations (IR)
    - Institut Francais des Relations Internationales - International Symposium on the Future of Lebanon (IR 8501), 1984-1987 (Box 49, Folder 289-290)
      Folder 290 - Supplementary Material
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies - Governance in a World Economy (IR 8509), 1982-1987 (Box 50, Folder 291-293)
    - United Nations Association of the United States of America, Economic Policy Council - Study of U. S. Policy Toward Emerging Industrial Countries (IR 8512), 1985-1987 (Box 50, Folder 294-295)
    - Columbia University - Urmila Phadnis, South Asian Regional Security Project (IR 8520), 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 296)
    - Global Interdependence Center - International Monetary and Trade Conference (IR 8522), 1982-1986 (Box 51, Folder 297-300)
    - Southern Africa - U.S.-Soviet Dialogue on Southern Africa (IR 8523), 1984-1986 (Box 51, Folder 301-302, Box 52, Folder 303-307, Box 53, Folder 308-310)
    - International Economic Association - Conference (IR 8525), 1985-1989 (Box 53, Folder 311, Box 54, Folder 312-314)
      Folders 312-314 - Supplementary Material
    - Western Australian Institute of Technology - Publication of "Perspectives on International Relations in the Indian Ocean Region" (IR 8526), 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 315)
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - West European Program (IR 8527), 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 316)
    - University of Pittsburgh - "Security Outside NATO: The Atlantic Alliance and the Middle East" (IR 8530), 1984-1988 (Box 54, Folder 317, Box 55, Folder 318-320)
      Folders 318-320 - Supplementary Material
    - The American Assembly - "Easing East-West Tensions in the Third World" (IR 8532), 1984-1987 (Box 55, Folder 321, Box 56, Folder 322)
    - Roman Laba - Research on Solidarity Movement in Poland (IR 8533), 1983-1987 (Box 56, Folder 323-325, Box 57, Folder 326)
    - Center for a New Democracy - Conference, "Transitions in the Pacific Rim: Leadership for the Next Twenty Years" (IR 8534), 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 327)
    - Overseas Development Council - World Bank Future Directions (IR 8536), 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 328)
    - World Peace Foundation - Inter-American Collective Security Project (IR 8537), 1985-1987 (Box 57, Folder 329)
    - Georgetown University - Conference, "African Debt and Financing" (IR 8538), 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 330-331)
    - William C. Potter - Development of Educational Materials for Simulating Arms Control Negotiations (IR 8541), 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 332)
    - Journal of Interdisciplinary History - Conference, "The Origins and Prevention of War" (IR 8601), 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 333)
    - African Association of Political Science - Workshop, "Whither South Africa" (IR 8604), 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 334)
    - International Human Rights Law Group - Fact-Finding/Trial Observer Mission to Liberia (IR 8605), 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 335)
    - Darko Bekich - Soviet Policy Toward Yugoslavia and the Balkans (IR 8606), 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 336)
    - Institute for International Economics - "Agriculture and the GATT: Issues in a New Trade Round" (IR 8607), 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 337)
    - Emory University, Carter Center - Symposium, "The Debt Crisis: Adjusting to the Past or Planning for the Future?" (IR 8608), 1985-1987 (Box 59, Folder 338-339)
    - Graduate Institute of International Studies (Geneva) - Conference, "War, Society and Politics: Iran and Iraq, 1980-86" (IR 8612), 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 340)
    - New York Academy of Sciences - Conference, "The High Technologies and Reducing the Risk of War" (IR 8615), 1985-1987 (Box 59, Box 341)
    - Fundación Mediterránea - Latin American Meeting of the Econometric Society (IR 8622), 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 342, Box 60, Folder 343-345)
    - Mitchell G. Reiss - Nuclear Non-proliferation, India Case Study (IR 8623), 1985-1987, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 346)
    - Chinese Scholars of International Studies, Inc. - Symposium, "Chinese Foreign Policy in the 1980s" (IR 8624), 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 347-348)
    - Church of the Pilgrims - Network for Human Rights in Liberia (IR 8625), 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 349)
      Scope and Contents
      Ellen Johnson-Sirleaf
    - Institute for International Economics - Conference (IR 8631), 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 350)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - Conference (PS 8504), 1984-1987 (Box 61, Folder 351)
    - University of Connecticut - Guinea Pig Sperm Antigens (PS 8507), 1984-1986, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 352)
    - Population Council - Symposium on Immunologic Approaches to Contraception and Promotion of Fertility (PS 8509), 1984-1987 (Box 61, Folder 353)
    - University of Massachusetts - Progesterone (PS 8510), 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 354)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Study of the Consequences of Population Growth and the Effectiveness of Family Planning Programs (PS 8511), 1983-1987 (Box 61, Folder 355)
    - International Women's Health Coalition - Symposium on the Prevention and Treatment of Contraceptive Failure (PS 8512), 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 356)
    - Federal University of Bahia - Ivan Mascarenhas (PS 8513), 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 357-357A)
      Folder 357A - Closed material - transcripts
    - El Colegio de México - Latin American Regional Population and Development Program (PS 8517), 1985-1988 (Box 62, Folder 358)
    - Cornell University - Immunological Consequences of Sperm Antibody Formation (PS 8520), 1983-1986 (Box 62, Folder 359)
    - Melkizedick T. Leshabari - "School Pregnancy and the Need for Sex Education in Tanzanian Schools" (PS 8521), 1984-1988 (Box 62, Folder 360)
      Also spelled "Melkizedeck"
    - The American Assembly, Columbia University - Assembly and Reports on International Population Policy (PS 8526), 1985-1988 (Box 62, Folder 361, Box 63, Folder 362)
    - Luis Rosero-Bixby - Proximate Determinants of Fertility in Costa Rica (PS 8527), 1985-1989 (Box 63, Folder 363)
    - Catholic University of Chile - Xth Meeting of Asociación Latinoamericana de Investigaciones en Reproducción Humana (PS 8528), 1985-1988 (Box 63, Folder 364)
    - Rockefeller University - Research on the Control of Reproduction by Catechol Estrogens (PS 8531), 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 365)
    - Rockefeller University - Studies on the Mechanism of Progestin Action in Reproductive Function (PS 8532), 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 366)
    - Instituto de Biología y Medicina Experimental - Unoccupied Estrogen Receptors in the Nuclei of the Anterior Pituitary (PS 8601), 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 367)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory (Woods Hole) - Video Microscopy Training (PS 8602), 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 368)
    - Akbar Aghajanian - Fertility and the Value of Children in Iran (PS 8611), 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 369)
    - McMaster University - Indian Scientists' Travel to International Congress of Reproductive Immunology (PS 8613), 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 370)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - University of Nairobi - Women's Issues (SIE 8504), 1984-1986 (Box 64, Folder 371)
    - Peter Magubane - Photographic Study on the Role of Women in South Africa (SIE 8505), 1984-1988 (Box 64, Folder 372)
    - Council on Foundations - "Third International Conference of Foundations and Business Leaders" (SIE 8508), 1985-1987 (Box 64, Folder 373)
    - Obor, Inc. - Special Issue of "Solidarity" on the Topic of Ideology and Modernization (SIE 8511), 1983-1988 (Box 64, Folder 374-376)
    - National Museums of Kenya - Development of International Field School of Palaeoanthropology (SIE 8512), 1984-1987 (Box 64, Folder 377)
    - The World Bank - Rockefeller Foundation and Indian Agricultural Development, Archival Research (SIE 8513), 1984-1987, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 378)
      International Bank for Reconstruction and Development
    - University of Georgia Law School Association - Dean Rusk Papers, Archival Collection (SIE 8514), 1984-1987, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 379)
    - Williams College - Conference on "Development Policies and Economics Training" (SIE 8516), 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 380-381)
      Grant Title: Conference on "Development Politics and Economics Training"
    - Penelope E. Andrews (SIE 8517), 1984-1988 (Box 65, Folder 382)
    - Women In Need, Inc. - Child Care Service (SIE 8520), 1985-1988 (Box 65, Folder 383)
    - New York University - Study on Modern Portfolio Management and the Prudent Man Rule (SIE 8523), 1984-1987 (Box 65, Folder 384)
    - Partnership for Productivity International - Conference to Develop a Response to the African Food Crisis (SIE 8525), 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 385)
    - Indiana University - Meeting of Africanist Scholars and Museum Professionals (SIE 8529), 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 386)
    - Women's Funding Coalition - Workshop to Consider Future Directions of Development Alternatives with Women for a New Era (DAWN) (SIE 8530), 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 387-390)
    - International Institute for Environment and Development - Private Sector Activity of the United Nations Office for Emergency Operations in Africa (SIE 8531), 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 391, Box 67, Folder 392)
    - Robert E. Kohler - History of Philanthropy and Science (SIE 8532), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 393)
    - National Council for Research on Women - Establishing an Institutional Base for the Women's Dialogue - US/USSR (SIE 8533), 1984-1988 (Box 67, Folder 394-395)
    - Susan M. Okin - "Justice and Gender" (SIE 8535), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 396)
    - University of California (Los Angeles) - "Men, Women and Wheels" The Relationship Between Gender and Mobility in American Society" (SIE 8537), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 397)
    - Harvard University - "Women's Contribution to the Family Economy: A Cross-National Study" (SIE 8538), 1985-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 398)
    - Mary Beth Norton - "Gender and Society in Seventeenth-Century America" (SIE 8539), 1985-1987, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 399)
    - Cornell University - "Children's Thinking About Gender" (SIE 8540), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 400)
    - Social Science Research Council - Foreign Language and International Studies (SIE 8602), 1984-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 401-403, Box 69, Folder 404-405)
    - Aga Khan Foundation U.S.A. - Conference, "The Enabling Environment for Effective Private Sector Contribution to Development in Sub-Saharan Africa" (SIE 8606), 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 406)
    - Centre Internationale de Liaison des Ecoles de Cinema et de Television (CILECT) - Training in Developing Countries (SIE 8607), 1985-1988 (Box 69, Folder 407-408)
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies - Seminar on the Role of Philanthropy and Nonprofit Institutions (SIE 8608), 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 409)
    - Workshop on Gender, Technology and Development (SIE 8609), 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 410-411)
      Workshop was co-sponsored by the Rockefeller Foundation and the International Development Research Centre.
    - Independent Sector - Forum and Guidebook on Community Service (SIE 8611), 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 412)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - Carlos Brambila Paz (RF 85043 - PS), 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 413-413A)
      Folder 413A - Closed Material - Medical and personal information
    - Claudio Fabian Chillik (RF 85009 - PS), 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 414-414A)
      Folder 414A - Closed Material - Medical and personal information
    - Edward Luiz Gonçalves Rios-Neto (RF 86091 - PS), 1985-1987 (Box 71, Folder 415-415A)
      Folder 415A - Closed Material - Medical and personal information
    - Cecilia Vilar-Rojas (RF 85034 - PS), 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 416-416A)
      Folder 416A - Closed Material - Medical information
    - Sichuan Medical College - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A40), 1985, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 417)
    - Third Annual Meeting of the International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) (RF 85004) (A42), 1984-1986 (Box 71, Folder 418-419)